Choose some bread and a drink for breakfast.
Aye-aye!
Without running!
That kid just doesn't listen.
Now... for a cold, we have water, sports drinks...
dairy products, and so on...
What kind of food goes down easily?
Rin, do you wanna get something for breakfast, too?
Cereal or something?
Sure...
Daikichi...
Did I make her sick?
Rin...
Cold viruses are all over the place.
Some will catch it and some won't.
There's no reason to worry about where it came from.
Can I pick something to bring her too?
Sure.
This...
Put it in the basket.
Kouki!
What are you doing in the snacks aisle?!
Kouki! What about breakfast?
It came out!
Bunny Drop
I dunno about tomorrow
It's different than a sacrifice Something's off
I don't think it's like some penalty game
So, why? I don't get it at all
I'm a little bit unsatisfied, but your presence
right now is more than just important
There's no such thing in this world
as something never-ending
Crying isn't painful, it's love's sweet drops, sweet drops!
I want to keep dreaming forever, ya know?
I want to be more kind, ya know?
As long as I'm with you, I'm happy
Girls sure are strong, ya know?
But sometimes we're weak, ya know?
Our wish is to be happy, happy, happy!
And those days will be happy, too!
Just wanna make you happy!
I live here!
We're gonna head home.
I don't want your mom fussing over us.
Okay.
Here. Give this food to your mom.
It's heavy.
It's really heavy...
Well, let's go, Rin.
Mom! Daikichi gave us food!
Listen when somebody's talking to you!
Kouki, you don't have to...
Daikichi...
Sorry for making you look after him all the time...
O-Oh, no, I owe you for taking care of Rin...
How is Rin?
She's a lot better now.
She went back to school today. Right?
Hello...
Hello. I'm glad you're feeling better, Rin.
Yeah.
I'm making that rice gruel right now.
I'll be better soon too.
Yep.
Rin, let's go throw my tooth!
This way!
Kouki, be careful.
Gotcha!
Nitani, you probably caught your cold when you were taking care of Rin...
I'm sorry.
We're gonna throw it from here!
I meet a lot of people every day.
It's so high up...
The train I take to the office is always packed.
I'm gonna throw it on that roof.
There's no telling where it came from.
Don't worry about it.
It's just a cold.
Okay.
Well, at least let me help with Kouki.
I can pick him up from day care.
Thank you.
Rin, we're going home.
Daikichi, let's play video games!
Sure. Next time.
Kouki, make sure to help your mom out.
Okay.
Oh, that's right.
The small bottle and pudding are from Rin.
Thank you, Rin!
Pudding is my favorite!
Good night.
Daikichi, hurry up!
You're up early... It's Sunday!
I told you I'm going to practice for the jump rope contest!
What's wrong?
This one's wobbly too...
Brush slowly.
Okay...
Don't mess with it!
Oww!
Please don't push yourself too hard.
Oh, I'm fine now.
I'm sorry for always taking advantage of your generosity.
I think it's the other way around.
Really, thank you.
Not at all.
I'm surprised at Kouki...
For some reason, he just can't get it.
Kouki, you're jumping too soon.
When the jump rope swings around, you jump here, right?
Yeah.
Then you can't move your arms and legs at the same time.
I see...
Your arms go first, then your legs.
Try it once slowly.
Got it!
Daikichi! Me too! Me too!
Okay, okay. Rin, you're swinging your arms too far out.
Keep your arms in close like this...
Daikichi!
You're early, huh?!
Good morning!
Well, aren't they energetic?
Nobu's pretty good.
It's his big brother.
Nobu mimics everything he does.
Huh...
Aren't you gonna join them, Sayaka?
This time, she lost one of her upper teeth...
Girls have it rough, even when they're little kids...
Sayaka, what kind of container are you using to hold your teeth?
Did your parents buy you a cute one?
A cute what?
Do you know those cases people use to hold their kids' baby teeth as a keepsake?
Keepsake?
They have these cute tiny ones.
Tiny!
Cute!
Right?
Yeah! Mine is a butterfly!
I bought one for Kouki, but...
I bet Rin would love that!
We're saving the kids' teeth, too.
I'm such an idiot! I had no idea those existed!
It's been like this ever since I met Rin.
Fretting and getting nervous over the littlest things...
Daikichi, this is for you.
I drew it at school.
Daikichi
The stew Daikichi makes is really delicious.
Also, Daikichi can run really fast.
I had to write about someone at home.
Ah, well...
It's so cute!
What is this?
You put your baby teeth in there when they come out.
It's like a keepsake...
A keepsake!
Thank you, Mrs. Nitani!
You're welcome.
Thank you.
But isn't that Kouki's...?
Don't worry about it. It's fine...
I throw my teeth!
...as you can see.
I've been throwing my teeth on the roof.
Is that okay?
Yeah, that's fine.
You can do whichever one you want.
I see.
Rin! I'm gonna do my best with this jump rope thing, too!
You're touching your tooth again...
It'll come out on its own.
No matter what, she's gonna look like someone punched her.
As long as she doesn't smile...
There you go.
Good. Okay, let's go.
Did you grow again?
Huh? You too, Daikichi?
I'm starting to get a spare tire...
Me too!
It's tough when you get to be our age.
I just want to stop it.
Daikichi's doing it boxer-style!
That's amazing!
It's easier on the knees this way.
Huh...
Daikichi! Teach me how to do that, too!
Forget about it!
What?! Only you get to look cool?!
Learn how to jump rope normally first!
What was that?!
Get back here!
Me too! Me too!
Rin, you're so good at doing it backwards!
Wow, kids are incredible...
Really?
They have energy to burn, don't they?
Rock, paper, scissors!
I don't know where they get it from...
One more time!
Although adults are incredible, too...
Adults?
I think you two already know this, but I'm not Rin's dad.
We've only been living together for about a year now.
Before that, I used all my time for myself.
But once I started living with Rin, my lifestyle suddenly changed...
You guys have been with your kids ever since they were born though...
I've just started, so it's no big deal right now...
but I wonder if you guys are fine with no "me-time" down the line.
I'm fine...
Me too!
Me too.
Really?
Well, after all...
What? What?!
Rin, come to think of it, wasn't today the jump rope contest?
Yeah...
Rin...
I screwed up...
How many times?
15 times.
That's awful!
What about backwards-style jumping?
203 times.
You can jump like that?!
I'm gonna guess you got first place for that?
Yeah.
Here's my certificate.
Certificate of Merit
1st year division
1st place, backwards-style jumping rope
Kaga Rin
You really did your best. This is fantastic.
But I know I could've done better with regular-style.
Well, they only gave you one chance...
Yeah...
Well it's true you learned a lot about jumping rope.
I know it, at least.
Right.
I lost weight!
Huh?
Cut it out!
Are we almost there?
Maybe 10 more minutes...
They'll want to see those wobbly front teeth.
Right!
How many times do I have to tell you? Don't touch them if you can help it!
And I'll show them how I can jump rope, too!
Of course.
You've shot up since the last time.
I bet my mom and dad will be surprised.
I wonder if I'm taller than Auntie now.
I don't think you're that tall yet.
I'll have to tell Grandpa, too.
We're back!
Oh, Rin! I've been waiting for you!
I'm home.
Look at how big you've gotten!
Are you one of the taller kids in your class?
Yeah!
If you'd called, I would've picked you up at the station!
Rin can walk 10 minutes!
Soon, you'll be taller than me!
Kazumi!
Yo. You're here early.
Yeah, I just got here a little while ago.
Those clothes...
You used to wear them, right?
Yeah...
Auntie sent them to me!
Rin, show me your teeth.
Okay!
Two of the front ones are wobbly...
Are you okay? It doesn't hurt?
Only sometimes, but I'm used to it.
I'm a pro, see?
Hey, Daikichi!
Isn't there anything you can do for her?!
Her gums are turning red!
There isn't much...
And come to think of it, you wanted to yank out my loose teeth with a thread when I was a kid!
A thread?!
Oh my goodness! Did I really?!
I tried to make everything soft.
Thank you!
Wanna have some dried tofu?
Yeah!
I'll have boiled beans too, Auntie!
Sure!
Eat up!
I love dried tofu!
Did one come out?
Rin?
It came out!
Blood! Blood!
Mom! Tissue! Tissue!
Hold on! Hold on!
I'm fine!
Rin, use this for now!
That's a dust cloth!
Rin has changed a lot.
I don't know...
This is probably the real Rin.
Huh...
So, you're getting married?
Mom mentioned it.
Yeah.
Good for you. She said he seemed like a nice guy.
Yeah, well...
The only thing I'm not on board with is that he wants to have a kid right away.
That's a good thing, isn't it?
Are you kidding me?!
I wouldn't be able to go out drinking or go to concerts
or go on trips or eat delicious food...
I wouldn't be able to do anything anymore!
Well, you gotta talk to your husband about that.
I wouldn't know...
I'm not into kids in the first place!
And I don't wanna become one of those pushy moms either!
I don't think I could sacrifice myself to raise a kid...
Ah, I think you'd manage somehow.
If you put your mind to it...
Sometimes you just have to manage...
Easy for you to say, Dai...
Yeah, maybe...
What's that?
I've never become a father or a husband, let alone a mother.
It's burning...
Yeah.
True, I don't have time to shop at my leisure,
or chat with friends over coffee...
But my time at work is my own time...
And my time with my son is also my time...
Precious time...
Other parents might look like it,
but I don't think they're doing anything special.
If you look around you, you'll see mothers and fathers everywhere like that.
I see...
Right...
Grandpa, you know what?
Some of my adult teeth are coming in.
Hey! Rin!
Th-This is sweat!
Daikichi!
Hurry up!
Say "cheese"!
That jar...
Masako had it too...
I'll be right back!
Daikichi!
What?! The other one's coming loose?!
Mirror! Mirror!
I'm sure I'll never stop getting worked up over little things.
I suppose it's the same way with those two...
Does it hurt?
Rin!
Daikichi, look at this!
What the heck? You look like a cat!
I know, right?
Send a text to Auntie!
You mean a photo?
Nevertheless, it seems like that smile will be my joy from now on...
Yeah!
Hurry up!
Okay, open your mouth.
I don't think there's anything wrong with that.
A sunny early Sunday afternoon
Let's go somewhere today
It's the same road I'm used to traveling
But I can see it sparkling so bright
With the sun shining down its warmth
And you here by my side...
I'm already high, high, high
I feel like dashing out
Sing, la, la, la
My voice out to forever
I'm already high, high, high
Ride the dancing wind
Sing, la, la, la
My voice springs up
Daikichi!